<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Imperial - Chain Sword -->

  <OGI_Melee_ChainSword.label>Цепной меч</OGI_Melee_ChainSword.label>
  <OGI_Melee_ChainSword.description>Цепной меч является предпочтительным оружием ближнего боя многих военных сил Империума Человечества. Цепной меч - это, по сути, меч с мощными зубьями, которые бегут по лезвию, как у бензопилы. Большинство версий оружия используют зубцы с мономолекулярными краями или другие острые как бритва зубы. Цепные мечи не являются тонким оружием, и владение ими является собой разумеющимся: они являются ужасными орудиями войны, предназначенными для того, чтобы кусать, рвать и раздирать, когда более примитивные клинки просто рубят и режут. Оружие издает злобный жужжащий звук, когда зубы кружатся, усиливаясь до пронзительного крика. Они мало чем отличается от современной бензопилы, но их легко можно держать одной рукой. Часто используется в сочетании с лазпистолетом.</OGI_Melee_ChainSword.description>
  <OGI_Melee_ChainSword.tools.0.label>навершие</OGI_Melee_ChainSword.tools.0.label>
  <OGI_Melee_ChainSword.tools.1.label>лезвие</OGI_Melee_ChainSword.tools.1.label>
  <OGI_Melee_ChainSword.tools.2.label>остриё</OGI_Melee_ChainSword.tools.2.label>


  <!-- Imperial - Eviscerator -->

  <OGI_Melee_Eviscerator.label>Потрошитель</OGI_Melee_Eviscerator.label>
  <OGI_Melee_Eviscerator.description>Потрошитель - двуручный цепной меч, который используют Сёстры Битвы и особо фанатичные служители Культа Императора. Кроме того имеет слабое силовое поле..</OGI_Melee_Eviscerator.description>
  <OGI_Melee_Eviscerator.tools.0.label>лезвие</OGI_Melee_Eviscerator.tools.0.label>
  <OGI_Melee_Eviscerator.tools.1.label>остриё</OGI_Melee_Eviscerator.tools.1.label>


  <!-- Imperial - Power Sword -->

  <OGI_Melee_PowerSword.label>Силовой меч</OGI_Melee_PowerSword.label>
  <OGI_Melee_PowerSword.description>Силовой меч — силовое оружие, меч произвольной длины и конструкции, изготавливаемый из множества различных материалов, как правило — адамантия. Когда его силовой аккумулятор активируется (обычно — нажатием кнопки управления, расположенной на рукоятке), лезвие окружается смертоносным ореолом разрушительной энергии. Это энергетическое поле позволяет лезвию прорезать плоть, кости и большинство защитных доспехов, что делает силовой меч эффективным оружием ближнего боя. Силовые мечи используются воинами всех родов войск Империума, включая войска Имперской Гвардии и космодесантников Адептус Астартес. Ксенорасы, такие как эльдары, их падшие родичи тёмные эльдары и некроны, также применяют подобное оружие..</OGI_Melee_PowerSword.description>
  <OGI_Melee_PowerSword.tools.0.label>лезвие</OGI_Melee_PowerSword.tools.0.label>
  <OGI_Melee_PowerSword.tools.1.label>остриё</OGI_Melee_PowerSword.tools.1.label>


  <!-- Imperial - Power Axe -->

  <OGI_Melee_PowerAxe.label>Силовой топор</OGI_Melee_PowerAxe.label>
  <OGI_Melee_PowerAxe.description>A Power Axe is a Power Weapon that has been shaped into an axe of varying size and design crafted from one of any number of different materials, though usually Adamantium. When its power cell is activated, often by touching a control located on the haft, the blade is sheathed in a lethal corona of disruptive energy. This energy field allows the blade to carve through flesh, bone and most forms of armour plate alike, making a Power Axe a highly effective Imperial close combat weapon. Power Axes are used by all members of the Imperial armed forces, including the troops of the Imperial Guard and the Space Marines of the Adeptus Astartes.</OGI_Melee_PowerAxe.description>
  <OGI_Melee_PowerAxe.tools.0.label>лезвие</OGI_Melee_PowerAxe.tools.0.label>


  <!-- Imperial - Lightning Claw (Single) -->

  <OGI_Melee_LightningClawS.label>Грозовой коготь</OGI_Melee_LightningClawS.label>
  <OGI_Melee_LightningClawS.description>A Lightning Claw is a specialised type of Power Weapon, most commonly used by Space Marine Assault and Terminator Squads. It consists of a powered gauntlet fitted with three or four razor-sharp Adamantium blades, each a miniature power weapon sheathed in a matter disrupting power field, enabling them to carve through armour and flesh with ease. Lightning claws are often wielded in pairs and are mostly commonly used by Terminator Assault Squads. An entire squad can be armed with a pair each, but the weapon can also be used singly or in pairs by any individual with access to the Chapter's Armoury. Lightning Claws are a standard weapon primarily utilised by battle-brothers of the Adeptus Astartes, the daemon-hunting Inquisitors of the Ordo Malleus and Chaos Space Marines.</OGI_Melee_LightningClawS.description>
  <OGI_Melee_LightningClawS.tools.0.label>лезвие</OGI_Melee_LightningClawS.tools.0.label>
  <OGI_Melee_LightningClawS.tools.1.label>остриё</OGI_Melee_LightningClawS.tools.1.label>


  <!-- Imperial - Lightning Claw (Dual) -->

  <OGI_Melee_LightningClawD.label>Двойные грозовые когти</OGI_Melee_LightningClawD.label>
  <OGI_Melee_LightningClawD.description>A Lightning Claw is a specialised type of Power Weapon, most commonly used by Space Marine Assault and Terminator Squads. It consists of a powered gauntlet fitted with three or four razor-sharp Adamantium blades, each a miniature power weapon sheathed in a matter disrupting power field, enabling them to carve through armour and flesh with ease. Lightning claws are often wielded in pairs and are mostly commonly used by Terminator Assault Squads. An entire squad can be armed with a pair each, but the weapon can also be used singly or in pairs by any individual with access to the Chapter's Armoury. Lightning Claws are a standard weapon primarily utilised by battle-brothers of the Adeptus Astartes, the daemon-hunting Inquisitors of the Ordo Malleus and Chaos Space Marines.</OGI_Melee_LightningClawD.description>
  <OGI_Melee_LightningClawD.tools.0.label>лезвие</OGI_Melee_LightningClawD.tools.0.label>
  <OGI_Melee_LightningClawD.tools.1.label>остриё</OGI_Melee_LightningClawD.tools.1.label>


  <!-- Imperial  - Power Fist -->

  <OGI_Melee_PowerFistS.label>Силовой кулак</OGI_Melee_PowerFistS.label>
  <OGI_Melee_PowerFistS.description>A Power Fist (also known as a Power Glove) is essentially an over-sized, armoured gauntlet that generates an energy field around it, one that is capable of violently disrupting any solid matter it touches. It is a favoured close combat weapon for many warriors of the Imperium of Man, as well as the Forces of Chaos (particularly the Chaos Space Marines). It is especially an iconic weapon of the Loyalist Space Marines. A Power Fist is large and slow in combat, and so the bearer must be willing to risk the blows of his enemy before he can strike back. However, a Power Fist vastly augments a user's strength, much as Power Armour does due to the power provided its mechanical servos. The disadvantages of its unwieldy nature are often well worth the limitations, as the combination of the disruptive power field and sheer physical strength afforded by a Power Fist allows a Space Marine to pulverize and tear apart armour plate from even the most well-protected of vehicles, and to wound and kill colossal monstrous creatures in close combat; its brutal effects against more mundane foes goes without saying. It is most commonly found fitted to Space Marine Tactical Dreadnought (Terminator) Armour.</OGI_Melee_PowerFistS.description>
  <OGI_Melee_PowerFistS.tools.0.label>кулак</OGI_Melee_PowerFistS.tools.0.label>


  <!-- Imperial  - Chain Fist -->

  <OGI_Melee_ChainFistS.label>цепной кулак</OGI_Melee_ChainFistS.label>
  <OGI_Melee_ChainFistS.description>A Chainfist is a standard pattern Power Fist that has been fitted with a Chainsword attachment that is intented to allow its wielder to carve his way through armoured bulkheads. Originally designed for penetrating the armoured hulls of voidships during spaceborne boarding actions, the whirring adamantium blades of a Chainfist have long since proven their worth when engaging armoured targets of all kinds. Both Loyalist Terminators and Chaos Terminators often replace their armour's standard Power Fist with a Chainfist for use against enemy armoured vehicles and static defences in close combat.</OGI_Melee_ChainFistS.description>
  <OGI_Melee_ChainFistS.tools.0.label>кулак</OGI_Melee_ChainFistS.tools.0.label>


  <!-- Imperial  - Power Maul -->

  <OGI_Melee_PowerMaul.label>Силовая булава</OGI_Melee_PowerMaul.label>
  <OGI_Melee_PowerMaul.description>A Power Maul is an Imperial Power Weapon most commonly used by the Adeptus Arbites. Effectively a baton surrounded by a power field, the power maul has a hidden subtlety: the power field setting can be extensively adjusted so that its disruption effect can vary from bashing a hole through a wall, to delivering a sudden knock-out blow to an individual. This tactical depth-of-use makes it a valued tool of Imperial law enforcement. Arbites shock troops employ the weapon in combination with the suppression shield in breaking up riots. A similar weapon is the shock maul, which uses an electrical discharge instead of a power field to incapacitate the enemy.</OGI_Melee_PowerMaul.description>
  <OGI_Melee_PowerMaul.tools.0.label>навершие</OGI_Melee_PowerMaul.tools.0.label>


  <!-- Imperial  - Thunder Hammer -->

  <OGI_Melee_ThunderHammer.label>Громовой молот</OGI_Melee_ThunderHammer.label>
  <OGI_Melee_ThunderHammer.description>A Thunder Hammer is a melee Power Weapon often employed by Loyalist Space Marines of the Imperium of Man and by some Chaos Space Marines as well. Thunder Hammers are primarily used by Space Marines armoured in Terminator Armour. This large warhammer incorporates an energy field emitter within its head that activates only when the hammer strikes its target. This allows the weapon to store a tremendous amount of energy and release it only at the moment of impact, producing a terrific blast of energy and concussive force like the crack of thunder, from which the name of the weapon originates.</OGI_Melee_ThunderHammer.description>
  <OGI_Melee_ThunderHammer.tools.0.label>лезвие</OGI_Melee_ThunderHammer.tools.0.label>


  <!-- Imperial  - Guardian Spear -->

  <OGI_Melee_GuardianSpear.label>копье стража</OGI_Melee_GuardianSpear.label>
  <OGI_Melee_GuardianSpear.description>The Guardian Spear has been the signature weapon of the Adeptus Custodes since the time of the Unification Wars in the 30th Millennium, and in many ways their symbol of office. Elegant and deadly, it is a potent and unique design incorporating a Power Blade and a highly advanced integrated Bolter weapon, and in the hands of a Custodian Guard it can strike and parry at blinding speed despite its size. More rarely, these weapons mount not Bolters but advanced specialised sub-weapons such as compact Meltas or even Adrathic Disintegration Beamers, issued against the deadliest of expected foes.</OGI_Melee_GuardianSpear.description>
  <OGI_Melee_GuardianSpear.tools.0.label>древко</OGI_Melee_GuardianSpear.tools.0.label>
  <OGI_Melee_GuardianSpear.tools.1.label>остриё</OGI_Melee_GuardianSpear.tools.1.label>
  <OGI_Melee_GuardianSpear.tools.2.label>лезвие</OGI_Melee_GuardianSpear.tools.2.label>


  <!-- Imperial  - Force Staff -->

  <OGI_Melee_ForceStaff.label>силовой посох</OGI_Melee_ForceStaff.label>
  <OGI_Melee_ForceStaff.description>Force Weapons are advanced, psychically-attuned close combat weapons that are only effective in the hands of a psyker. Force Weapons effectively act as deadly, psychic extensions or amplifiers of the wielder's own Empyrean-spawned powers. They are designed to allow a psyker to channel deadly Warp energies into their victim, acting as a conduit between the wielder's mind and the flesh of his target. Large alien monstrosities and daemons that are resilient to conventional weapons can be slain outright by a single wound from a Force Weapon, as their bodies and minds are destroyed by the unearthly powers of the Immaterium.</OGI_Melee_ForceStaff.description>
  <OGI_Melee_ForceStaff.tools.0.label>черенок</OGI_Melee_ForceStaff.tools.0.label>
  <OGI_Melee_ForceStaff.tools.1.label>навершие</OGI_Melee_ForceStaff.tools.1.label>
  <OGI_Melee_ForceStaff.tools.2.label>силовой удар</OGI_Melee_ForceStaff.tools.2.label>


</LanguageData>